<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthew Hyatt</title>
    <link>https://mhyatt000.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matthew Hyatt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://mhyatt000.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mhyatt000.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:37:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhyatt000.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Computer Science major at Loyola University Chicago. Some of my hobbies include hiphop dance, weight lifting, and construction projects. I have close ties to my extended family and it is a long standing tradition for us to have Sunday night dinner together.
I first became interested in computer science during my high school classes. I have always been fascinated by the idea of efficiency, and using tools in order to complete goals in innovative ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clubs and Organizations</title>
      <link>https://mhyatt000.github.io/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:37:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhyatt000.github.io/groups/</guid>
      <description>These are some of the Loyola affiliated groups I participate in during my free time.
 Rambler Investment Fund (RIF)    RIF is a student managed portfolio valued at over 1 million dollars. RIF provides students with opportunities to build skills in financial analysis and risk assessment as well as to network with industry professionals.
I am a developer on RIF&amp;rsquo;s quantitative analytics team and write software to automate and visualize stock analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://mhyatt000.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:37:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhyatt000.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>DOI  DOI  10.5281/zenodo.5636779  10.5281/zenodo.5636779      
 Hyatt, Matt, Kuhl, Amy, Palmer, Jake, Sethi, Rohan, Synovic, Nicholas, Thiruvathukal, George, and Thota, Sohini. (2021). SSL Metrics Datasets (0.1) [Data set]. Zenodo. https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.5636779      DOI  DOI  10.5281/zenodo.6025973  10.5281/zenodo.6025973      
Hyatt, Matt, Kuhl, Amy, Palmer, Jake, Sethi, Rohan, Stoneman, Ethan, Synovic, Nicholas, Thota, Sohini, &amp;amp; Thiruvathukal, George K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://mhyatt000.github.io/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:37:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhyatt000.github.io/reading-list/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m constantly learning more about the world around me by reading the work of others. Here&amp;rsquo;s some of the ideas that I have been reading. Please send me any of your suggestions!
Research Papers     Language Models are Few-Shot Learners (GPT3) MapReduce Apache Hadoop YARN  Books     Python One-Liners  Christian Mayer   The Winner&amp;rsquo;s Curse  Richard H. Thaler   Basic Economics  Thomas Sowell   The Age of AI  Henry A.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
